lottomatic.info 2017-02-12

# LottoMatic.info - Privacy Policy

LottoMatic.info (also called "this website" on this disclaimer page) recognizes the importance of privacy of its visitors. Therefore, the visitors of this website should be aware of the following information.

## Usage Statistics

In order to generate usage statistics to help us improve this website, we automatically collect certain information on every visitor to this website. This information does not disclose "personal identifiers" (such as the name, address, Email address, phone number, etc.). Every time a page of this website is requested, a log file contianing generic user information is being created or updated. The information contained by the log file includes the type of Internet browser or computer operating system used to make the request, the date and time the page was requested, the Internet protocol address (or proxy server) of the individual computer that made the request, and the Internet address of the web page from which the visitor may have linked to this site. All information collected in the above mentioned log files can be used and may be analyzed for trends and statistics.

## Personal Information

This website will not collect personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, etc.). This website only collects non-personal information (such as Email address) and you are free to provide or to not provide the requested information. By choosing to not provide the non-personal information, you can still visit most of this website, but access to certain parts of this website will be restricted.

Any personal information voluntarily provided by visitors, including personal information submitted on online forms or any other pages of this website may be disclosed to third parties:

  * If we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.
  * If we are legally required to disclose your information.
  * To assist fraud reduction and minimize credit risks.

## Web Cookies

Visitors who submit information via this website should be aware that data linking your computer to this website (a so called "cookie") may be created by this website or a third party (such as Google). Temporary cookies may be used when necessary to complete a transaction, to process data submitted to us online or to facilitate ongoing Internet interaction. These cookies may also be subject to disclosure pursuant to a public records request.

## Google reCAPTCHA

The information collected by reCAPTCHA is held in accordance with the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

## Security Measures

The integrity of the information and systems that we maintain are taken very seriously by LottoMatic.info. Therefore, we have instituted security measures for information systems under our control. These security measures are designed to identify attempts to tamper with this Web site. Information collected through these security measures may be used in connection with a criminal prosecution or other legal proceedings.

## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this policy from time to time. This is a statement of policy and should not be interpreted as a contract of any kind. This Privacy Policy was last modified on July 31, 2016.

## Contact

Feel free to get in touch using the contact page or any of our social media channels:
